

I am a UI/UX designer with 7+ years of design experience, specializing in building scalable front-end products with great user experiences. I am currently looking for a hybrid UX designer and developer position to support between design and development.

## **PORTFOLIO**

jaykim-dev.netlify.app Website

# CONTACT

**Phone** +1 (469) 386-6307

**Email** develop.jay8675@gmail.com

**Address** Dallas, Texas

## **SOCIAL**

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/jay8675

**Github** github.com/jaehyung8675

## **SKILLS**

Design User Experience (UX)

User Interface (UI)

Product Graphic Visual

**Programming JavaScript** 

> React Node.js Express.js HTMI 5 CSS

Sass / SCSS

**Tools** Adobe XD

> Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator

Figma Git Github

Visual Studio Code

## **EXPERIENCE**

### Sr. UI/UX Designer

January 2020 - January 2023 Carrollton, Texas

**OTA World LLC** 

- Led a design team to create and enhance all visual design, and maintained company websites.
- Responsible for maintaining content and style attributes of marketing and e-commerce pages.
- Knowledge of content management applications and creative marketing tools.
- Designed and developed product pages using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS, and used by over 100+ merchants (Costco, Amazon, Sam's Club, Home Depot, etc.) to market their sites.
- Managed projects using Agile to quickly deliver products to stakeholders, vendors, and customers.

#### Visual Designer / Part-time

July 2017 - Present

Binnerri Presbyterian Church

Richardson, Texas

- Create all visual designs for over 400+ members to engage them in worship and events.
- Revamp 2+ websites to make them more visually and experientially accessible to customers.
- Create presentations for speakers to support their sermons and easily interact with the audience.
- Complete projects on time and deliver them to clients according to the church's schedule and goals.

#### **Graphic Designer**

January 2014 - December 2014

Ravis's Ware House

Dallas, Texas

- Created print materials such as brochures and flyers to promote products that helped increase sales.
- Implemented lighting and design in a studio environment to produce product images.

### **Product Designer** / Internship

January 2010 - January 2011

Pantech Wireless, Inc.

Seoul, South Korea

- Completed 2 major projects with all mobile design processes from concept to building mock-ups.
- Explored interactions and design ideas by creating storyboards, user flows, and prototypes.
- Collaborated with team members to implement new concept designs during the summer in Japan.

## **EDUCATION**

### **University of North Texas**

2020 - 2022

Denton, Texas M.A. in Interaction Design

**Southern Methodist University** 2017 - 2019

B.F.A. in Art & Graphic Design Dallas, Texas

**Brookhaven College** 2014 - 2017

A.A. in General Studies Farmers Branch, Texas

**Christian For The Nations Institute** 2012 - 2013

Accredited Theological Degree Dallas, Texas

**Hongik University** 2006 - 2010

B.A. in Product Design Sejong, South Korea